W. R. "Bob" Poage Personal papers, Inclusive: 1766-2008, undated, Bulk: 1937-1978
Baylor University Libraries
- Speeches, 1936-1986, undated; 4
  - “Should Yellow Oleomargarine be Prohibited from Commerce?”, Northwestern University Radio Forum, circa 1949 March (Box 61, Folder 29)
  - “The Farm Program of the Eighty First Congress,” Radio Broadcast, 1949 March 7 (Box 61, Folder 30)
  - Radio Broadcast on Secretary Brannan’s Texas Visit, 1949 March 27 (Box 61, Folder 31)
  - “Regulation of Oleomargarine,” “Congressional Record”, 1949 April 1 (Box 61, Folder 32)
  - “Texas Ginners,” Delivered in Dallas, 1949 April 14 (Box 61, Folder 33)
  - Press Releases, 1949 April 26 (Box 61, Folder 34)
  - “Brazos River Transmission Electric Cooperative,” News Release, 1949 April 29 (Box 61, Folder 35)
  - “Housing Legislation,” “Congressional Record”, 1949 June 29 (Box 61, Folder 36)
  - “Congressional Record”, 1949 July (Box 61, Folder 37)
  - “Congressional Record”, 1949 August 3 (Box 61, Folder 38)
  - Poage as Guest Columnist for “Temple Telegram” and “San Antonio Light”, 1949 September 14 (Box 61, Folder 39)
  - “Congressional Record”, 1949 October (Box 61, Folder 40)
  - “An American Defense Policy,” “Congressional Record”, 1949 November 4 (Box 61, Folder 41)
  - “Democracy Beats Communism,” Radio Speech over W-A-C-O, 1949 December 7 (Box 61, Folder 42)
  - “Cotton,” “Congressional Record”, 1950 January 30 (Box 61, Folder 43)
  - Statement to Ways and Means Committee, 1950 February 15 (Box 61, Folder 44)
  - “Congressional Record”, 1950 March (Box 61, Folder 45)
  - News Release on Cotton Allotments, 1950 March (Box 61, Folder 46)
  - “Congressional Record”, 1950 April (Box 61, Folder 47)
  - “Congressional Record”, 1950 May (Box 61, Folder 48)
  - Article for “Waco Tribune-Herald” on Rural Electrification Administration, 1950 May 10 (Box 61, Folder 49)
  - Fort Hood Dedication, 1950 May 26 (Box 61, Folder 50)
  - “Congressional Record”, 1950 June (Box 61, Folder 51)
  - Report on Rural Telephones, 1950 June 19 (Box 61, Folder 52)
  - “Congressional Record”, 1950 July (Box 61, Folder 53)
  - Political Campaign Speech delivered over K-W-T-X, 1950 July 6 (Box 61, Folder 54)
  - “Rural Electrification Administration”, 1950 July 13 (Box 61, Folder 55)
  - Radio Speech over W-A-C-O, K-T-E-M, and K-E-T-X, Broadcast from Washington, D.C., 1950 July 20 (Box 61, Folder 56)
  - “Congressional Record”, 1950 August (Box 61, Folder 57)
  - Address at Interparliamentary Union Conference, Dublin, Ireland, 1950 September (Box 61, Folder 58)
  - “Commemoration of Centenary of Death of San Martin,” Delivered at Interparliamentary Union Conference, Dublin, Ireland, 1950 September (Box 61, Folder 59)
  - “Defense Production Act of 1950,” “Congressional Record”, 1950 September 6 (Box 61, Folder 60)
  - Statement Delivered over W-F-A-M on Europe Trip, 1950 October 16 (Box 61, Folder 61)
  - “The Texas Tidelands Decision by the Supreme Court,” “Congressional Record”, 1950 October 16 (Box 61, Folder 62)
  - “Congressional Record”, 1950 December (Box 61, Folder 63)
  - “The Relation of Foreign Affairs to the American Farmer,” Delivered before the Annual Convention of American Farm Bureau Federation, Dallas, 1950 December 13 (Box 61, Folder 64)
  - “Congressional Record”, 1951 January (Box 62, Folder 1)
  - “Congressional Record”, 1951 February (Box 62, Folder 2)
  - “Congressional Record”, 1951 March (Box 62, Folder 3)
  - “Congressional Record”, 1951 April (Box 62, Folder 4)
  - McCloskey Hospital News Release, 1951 May 11 (Box 62, Folder 5)
  - “Conservation Appropriation,” “Congressional Record”, 1951 May 15 (Box 62, Folder 6)
  - “Office of Price Stabilization Roll Back on Meat,” Radio Speech Over Liberty Broadcasting, Dallas, 1951 May 25 (Box 62, Folder 7)
  - “What is Happening to our Meat Supply?”, Delivered to Texas Restaurant Association, Houston, 1951 June 7 (Box 62, Folder 8)
  - “Migratory Labor,” “Congressional Record”, 1951 June 26-27 (Box 62, Folder 9)
  - “Congressional Record”, 1951 July (Box 62, Folder 10)
  - Letter to the Editor of “Waco News Tribune”, 1951 July 27 (Box 62, Folder 11)
  - “Congressional Record”, 1951 August (Box 62, Folder 12)
  - “The Displaced Person,” Delivered at Interparliamentary Union Conference, Istanbul, Turkey, 1951 August (Box 62, Folder 13)
  - “Congressional Record”, 1951 September (Box 62, Folder 14)
  - “Congressional Record”, 1951 October (Box 62, Folder 15)
  - “Achievement Day,” Address to Farmers Home Administration, Dallas, 1951 October 10 (Box 62, Folder 16)
  - Tidelands Correspondence, 1951 November (Box 62, Folder 17)
  - Armistice Day Speech, Delivered at Fort Hood, 1951 November 10 (Box 62, Folder 18)
  - Address before Texas Farm Bureau Federation, Houston, 1951 November 20 (Box 62, Folder 19)
  - Address to Banquet for Texas Lineman at College Station, 1951 November 23 (Box 62, Folder 20)
  - Approval of Loan for Central Texas Telephone Cooperative of Goldthwaite, News Release, 1951 November 23 (Box 62, Folder 21)
  - Address to the Temple Lions Club, 1951 December 12 (Box 62, Folder 22)
  - News Release on Killeen-Area Housing, 1951 December 28 (Box 62, Folder 23)
  - “Appointment of a President’s Commission,” Press Release, 1952 January 7 (Box 62, Folder 24)
  - “Legislating for the Livestock Industry,” Delivered to American National Cattleman’s Association, Fort Worth, 1952 January 9 (Box 62, Folder 25)
  - “Utilization of Foreign Nationals in Our Armed Forces”, 1951 January 9 (Box 62, Folder 26)
  - “Military Pay Bill Goes Too Far,” “Congressional Record”, 1952 January 15 (Box 62, Folder 27)
  - “Enlargement of Fort Hood,” Press Release, 1952 February 5 (Box 62, Folder 28)
  - Address to National Association of Wheat Growers, Denver, Colorado, 1952 February 15 (Box 62, Folder 29)
  - “Congressional Record”, 1952 March (Box 62, Folder 30)
  - “Congressional Record”, 1952 April (Box 62, Folder 31)
  - “Congressional Record”, 1952 May (Box 62, Folder 32)
  - “Foot-and-Mouth Disease,” NBC Broadcast, 1952 May 2 (Box 62, Folder 33)
  - “Tidelands,” “Congressional Record”, 1952 June 11 (Box 62, Folder 34)
  - Re-Election Announcement, circa 1952 July (Box 62, Folder 35)
  - “Tax Subsidies Decision of the Defense Production Administration,” Press Release, 1952 July 1 (Box 62, Folder 36)
  - July 4th Address at Belton, Rockdale, and West, 1952 July 4 (Box 62, Folder 37)
  - Address to the League of Women Voters, Waco, 1952 July 18 (Box 62, Folder 38)
  - “Bob Cooper Named Rural Carrier,” Press Release, 1952 July 20 (Box 62, Folder 39)
  - Radio Address over K-W-T-X, 1952 July 25 (Box 62, Folder 40)
  - Address Before Interparliamentary Union Conference, Berne, Switzerland, 1952 September 1 (Box 62, Folder 41)
  - Statement on Tidelands, 1952 September 26 (Box 62, Folder 42)
  - Statement on Governor Stevenson, 1952 September 27 (Box 62, Folder 43)
  - Statement on Visit to Korean Battlefront, 1952 September 27 (Box 62, Folder 44)
  - Address to American Meat Institute, Chicago, Illinois, 1952 October 3 (Box 62, Folder 45)
  - Letter to Governor Shivers about McCloskey Hospital, 1952 October 9 (Box 62, Folder 46)
  - Letter to Mr. George Prowse about McCloskey Hospital, 1952 October 13 (Box 62, Folder 47)
  - Address at Democratic Rally for Stevenson-Sparkman Ticket, Waco, 1952 October 14 (Box 62, Folder 48)
  - Letter to Honorable R.C. Tompkins on Moore Field, 1952 October 17 (Box 62, Folder 49)
  - “Appropriation for Moore Field AND Transfer of Tubercular Patients to McCloskey Hospital, Temple, Texas,” Press Release, 1952 October 19 (Box 62, Folder 50)
  - Statements on President-Elect Eisenhower and Agriculture, 1952 November 6 (Box 62, Folder 51)
  - “Request for Special Freight Rates for Movement of Disaster Hay”, 1952 November 18 (Box 62, Folder 52)
  - “Congressional Record”, 1953 February (Box 62, Folder 53)
  - “Firing of Claude Wickard from Rural Electrification Administration”, 1953 March 17 (Box 62, Folder 54)
  - “Submerged Lands,” “Congressional Record”, 1953 March 31 (Box 62, Folder 55)
  - “Congressional Record”, 1953 April (Box 62, Folder 56)
  - “Expansion of Fort Hood”, 1953 April (Box 62, Folder 57)
  - News Release on Tidelands Decision, 1953 April 9 (Box 62, Folder 58)
  - Press Release on Korean Armistice, 1953 April 11 (Box 62, Folder 59)
  - “Congressional Record”, 1953 May (Box 62, Folder 60)
  - “Submerged Lands — Within the Historic Boundaries of the States — Who is Giving them Away?”, Regarding the Tidelands and Other Cases, circa 1953 May (Box 62, Folder 61)
  - “Congressional Record”, 1953 June (Box 62, Folder 62)
  - Statement to Foreign Aid Subcommittee of the House Appropriations Committee, 1953 June 4 (Box 62, Folder 63)
  - U.S. Merchant Marine Cadet Corps, News Release, 1953 June 23 (Box 62, Folder 64)
  - “Government Aid to Cattlemen as a Result of Drought”, 1953 June 24 (Box 62, Folder 65)
  - “Congressional Record”, 1953 July (Box 62, Folder 66)
  - July 4th Address in Belton, Rockdale, and West, 1953 July 4 (Box 62, Folder 67)
  - “Drought Relief,” News Release, 1953 July 15 (Box 62, Folder 68)
  - “End of Drought Relief Program in Bosque and Coryell Counties”, 1953 August-September (Box 62, Folder 69)
  - “Poage Continues to Fight for Upstream Flood Prevention,” Press Release, 1953 August 4 (Box 62, Folder 70)
  - “Drought Relief,” News Release, 1953 August 12 (Box 62, Folder 71)
  - “Farmers Need Credit for Unplanted Cotton Acreage,” Letter and Press Release, 1953 September 22 (Box 62, Folder 72)
  - “Upstream Flood Prevention,” Delivered at Dedication of Lower East Fork Project, Kaufman, 1953 September 29 (Box 63, Folder 1)
  - “Election of Lester Johnson, Democrat, in Wisconsin,” News Release, 1953 October 14 (Box 63, Folder 2)
  - “Reorganization of the Department of Agriculture (Soil Conservation Service),” Unused Article sent to Soil and Water Magazine, 1953 November (Box 63, Folder 3)
  - “‘Washington Viewpoint’ on Agriculture,” Delivered to Fort Worth Farm and Ranch Club, 1953 November 19 (Box 63, Folder 4)
  - “Annual Conference of the Food and Agriculture Organization,” Press Release, 1953 November 27 (Box 63, Folder 5)
  - “Cotton Acreage Allotment,” Press Release, 1953 December 5 (Box 63, Folder 6)
  - Introduction of Sam Rayburn at Democratic Dinner, Shrine Temple, Waco, 1953 December 15 (Box 63, Folder 7)
  - “Congressional Record”, 1954 January (Box 63, Folder 8)
  - Radio Broadcast with Senator Lyndon B. Johnson and Congressmen George H. Mahon, Lloyd Bentsen, Jack B. Brooks, 1954 February 8 (Box 63, Folder 9)
  - “Farm Prices and General Economic Conditions,” “Congressional Record”, 1954 February 17 (Box 63, Folder 10)
  - “Congressional Record”, 1954 March (Box 63, Folder 11)
  - “Air Force Academy,” Press Release, 1954 April 2 (Box 63, Folder 12)
  - “Federal Land Bank Purchases of Federal Farm Mortgage Corporation Assets,” “Congressional Record”, 1954 April 5 (Box 63, Folder 13)
  - Belton Reservoir Dedication, 1954 May 28 (Box 63, Folder 14)
  - “Congressional Record”, 1954 June (Box 63, Folder 15)
  - “Agricultural Act of 1954,” “Congressional Record”, 1954 July 1-2 (Box 63, Folder 16)
  - Parity, 1954 July 13 (Box 63, Folder 17)
  - “Congressional Record”, 1954 August (Box 63, Folder 18)
  - Interparliamentary Union Conference, Vienna, Austria, 1954 August (Box 63, Folder 19)
  - “What’s Ahead for America,” Delivered to Business and Professional Women’s Club, 1954 October 15 (Box 63, Folder 20)
  - “The Democratic Party,” Delivered to Young Democrats, Raleigh Hotel, Waco, 1954 November 14 (Box 63, Folder 21)
  - “Cotton Allotments,” “Farm Price Supports,” and “Livestock Support Prices”, circa 1954 December (Box 63, Folder 22)
  - “Federal Regulation of Production and Gathering of Natural Gas,” “Congressional Record”, 1955 January 10 (Box 63, Folder 23)
  - Statement on Rural Electrification in 1975, 1955 January 14 (Box 63, Folder 24)
  - “Congressional Record”, 1955 February (Box 63, Folder 25)
  - “Necessity of Better Understanding Between Grower and Consumer of Current Agricultural Problems,” Article Written for “Vee-Gee Messenger”, 1955 February 24 (Box 63, Folder 26)
  - “Do Consumers Pay Too Much for Food?” Article Written for “Soil and Water Magazine,” Temple, 1955 March 10 (Box 63, Folder 27)
  - “Farm Price Supports,” TV Production for K-A-N-G TV, Waco, 1955 March 22 (Box 63, Folder 28)
  - “Congressional Record”, 1955 April (Box 63, Folder 29)
  - “Price Supports,” TV Speech for K-C-E-N TV, Temple, 1955 April 22 (Box 63, Folder 30)
  - “Price of Food,” TV Speech for K-A-N-G TV, Temple, 1955 April 28 (Box 63, Folder 31)
  - “Four Ways of Securing Parity for Farmers,” TV Speech for K-C-E-N TV, Temple, 1955 April 29 (Box 63, Folder 32)
  - “Congressional Record”, 1955 May (Box 63, Folder 33)
  - “Price Support (H.R. 12 on Parity),” TV Speech for K-C-E-N TV, Temple, 1955 May 6 (Box 63, Folder 34)
  - “Agriculture and Foreign Trade,” TV Speech for K-C-E-N TV, Temple, 1955 May 12 (Box 63, Folder 35)
  - “You’ve Got to be Careful What You Brand Commie,” Newspaper Clipping, 1955 May 15 (Box 63, Folder 36)
  - “Poage Bill — H.R. 6304 (Education),” Press Release, 1955 May 17 (Box 63, Folder 37)
  - “Small Dam Program (Flood Prevention),” TV Speech for K-C-E-N TV, Temple, 1955 May 20 (Box 63, Folder 38)
  - Commencement Address Delivered at Oklahoma Baptist University, 1955 May 28 (Box 63, Folder 39)
  - “Farm Credit System,” TV Speech for K-C-E-N TV, Temple, 1955 May 28 (Box 63, Folder 40)
  - “Congressional Record”, 1955 June (Box 63, Folder 41)
  - “Price Supports on Grains,” TV Speech for K-C-E-N TV, Temple, 1955 June 11 (Box 63, Folder 42)
  - “Commodity Credit Corporation Stocks,” TV Speech for K-C-E-N TV, Temple, 1955 June 18 (Box 63, Folder 43)
  - “Recent Highlights in Congressman Poage’s Work for Central Texas,” TV Speech for K-A-N-G TV, Waco, 1955 June 22 (Box 63, Folder 44)
  - “Maneuvers,” TV Speech for K-C-E-N TV, Temple, 1955 June 22 (Box 63, Folder 45)
  - “Congressional Record”, 1955 July (Box 63, Folder 46)
  - “Farmer’s Banquet,” Delivered in McGregor, 1955 July 1 (Box 63, Folder 47)
  - “Mexican Labor Bill,” TV Speech for K-C-E-N TV, Temple, 1955 July 9 (Box 63, Folder 48)
  - Interparliamentary Speech, Helsinki, Finland, 1955 August (Box 63, Folder 49)
  - “Retirement of Government Capital in Institutions Operating under Supervision of Farm Credit Association,” “Congressional Record”, 1955 August 1 (Box 63, Folder 50)
  - News Release on Visit to Waco, 1955 August 6 (Box 63, Folder 51)
  - “The Possibility of Coexistence with Communism,” Delivered to Waco Rotary Club, 1955 August 15 (Box 63, Folder 52)
  - “Social Security” Radio Speech, 1955 September 26 (Box 63, Folder 53)
  - General Telegrams, 1955 October-November (Box 63, Folder 54)
  - News Releases, 1955 October (Box 63, Folder 55)
  - Radio Speech Delivered over K-M-I-L, Cameron, Texas, 1955 October 2 (Box 63, Folder 56)
  - News Release on Filing of Expense Account for South American Trip, 1955 December 1 (Box 63, Folder 57)
  - “Farm Price Supports,” Delivered at Bartlett Stag Dinner, Bartlett, Texas, 1955 December 28 (Box 63, Folder 58)
  - “Good Neighbor Policy,” “Congressional Record”, 1956 January 17 (Box 63, Folder 59)
  - News Release on Poage Self-Financing Cotton Program, 1956 January 20 (Box 63, Folder 60)
  - Briefs on H.R. 8703 and H.R. 8750, 1956 January 23-24 (Box 63, Folder 61)
  - Address to National Rural Electrification Administration Meeting, St. Louis, Missouri, 1956 January 25 (Box 63, Folder 62)
  - “Water,” Delivered to National Wool Growers Association, Fort Worth, 1956 January 26 (Box 63, Folder 63)
  - “Mr. Poage’s New Cotton Plan,” TV Speech for K-C-E-N TV, 1956 January 26 (Box 63, Folder 64)
  - “The Farm Problem — What's the Answer?” Conversation with Mr. Earl L. Butz to the American Forum, 1956 February 5 (Box 63, Folder 65)
  - Address to San Antonio Rotary Club, 1956 February 10 (Box 63, Folder 66)
  - “Rural Electrification Administration - Yesterday and Today,” “Congressional Record”, 1956 February 23 (Box 63, Folder 67)
  - TV Speech for K-C-E-N TV, 1956 February 25 (Box 63, Folder 68)
  - “The Soil Bank Plan,” TV Address for K-C-E-N TV, 1956 March 9 (Box 63, Folder 69)
  - “Flood Prevention Act Amendment,” TV Address to K-C-E-N TV, 1956 March 17 (Box 63, Folder 70)
  - Speech before National Women’s Democratic Club, Washington, D.C., 1956 March 26 (Box 63, Folder 71)
  - “The Soil Bank Plan as Recommended by the Agricultural Conferees on the Farm Bill,” TV Address for K-C-E-N TV, 1956 April 9 (Box 63, Folder 72)
  - “Speech on the Farm Bill on the Floor of the House”, 1956 April 11 (Box 63, Folder 73)
  - “The President’s Veto of the Farm Bill,” “Congressional Record”, 1956 April 17 (Box 64, Folder 1)
  - “The President’s Veto of the Farm Bill,” TV Speech to K-C-E-N TV, 1956 April 21 (Box 64, Folder 2)
  - “Speech on H.R. 8750, The Watershed Bill, on the Floor of the House”, 1956 April 24 (Box 64, Folder 3)
  - “Congressional Record”, 1956 May (Box 64, Folder 4)
  - “Feed Grain Provision of Farm Bill,” TV Address for K-C-E-N TV, 1956 May 19 (Box 64, Folder 5)
  - “Farm Bill,” TV Address for K-C-E-N TV, 1956 June 2 (Box 64, Folder 6)
  - Statement on Department of Agriculture, 1956 June 8 (Box 64, Folder 7)
  - TV Address for K-C-E-N TV, 1956 June 16 (Box 64, Folder 8)
  - “Supplemental Federal Reclamation Laws,” “Congressional Record”, 1956 June 12 (Box 64, Folder 9)
  - “Credit Facilities to Farmers and Amending Bankhead-Jones Farm Tenant Act,” “Congressional Record”, 1956 June 20 (Box 64, Folder 10)
  - “We Must Have Farm Price Supports or Depression,” Delivered to Old Cotton Belt Association, Rosebud, Texas, 1956 July 3 (Box 64, Folder 11)
  - “Why We Attempt to Support Farm Prices,” Delivered to Waco Kiwanis Club, 1956 July 3 (Box 64, Folder 12)
  - Address before Texas Senior Citizens Association, Waco, 1956 July 4 (Box 64, Folder 13)
  - “Postal Rates,” “Congressional Record”, 1956 July 6 (Box 64, Folder 14)
  - “To the Voters of the 11th District,” Newspaper Column, 1956 July 12 (Box 64, Folder 15)
  - TV Address to K-C-E-N TV, 1956 July 14 (Box 64, Folder 16)
  - “Civil Rights Bill,” “Congressional Record”, 1956 July 17 (Box 64, Folder 17)
  - Introduction of Senator Johnson at Heart O’ Texas Fair, Waco, 1956 October 1 (Box 64, Folder 18)
  - Address to Stanford Rotary Club, 1956 October 5 (Box 64, Folder 19)
  - Political Speech Delivered in Rosebud, Texas, 1956 October 19 (Box 64, Folder 20)
  - “Whether We Shall Eat,” Delivered to Waco Press Club, 1956 October 23 (Box 64, Folder 21)
  - Address to Business and Professional Women’s Club, Waco, 1956 October 26 (Box 64, Folder 22)
  - “Democratic Dinner,” Delivered in Waco, 1956 November 1 (Box 64, Folder 23)
  - Statement on Farm Prices, 1957 (Box 64, Folder 24)
  - Statement on Secretary Benson’s Meeting with Members of Congress, 1957 January 3 (Box 64, Folder 25)
  - “Drought Areas in the United States,” “Congressional Record”, 1957 January 10 (Box 64, Folder 26)
  - “Congressional Record”, 1957 February (Box 64, Folder 27)
  - “The Corn Bill,” TV Address for K-C-E-N TV, 1957 February 16 (Box 64, Folder 28)
  - “Corn and Feed Grain Programs,” “Congressional Record”, 1957 March 6-13 (Box 64, Folder 29)
  - “The Corn Bill,” TV Address for K-C-E-N TV, 1957 March 15 (Box 64, Folder 30)
  - “The Cowman’s Interest in Soil Bank Legislation,” Delivered to Texas & Southwestern Cattle Raisers Association, 1957 March 20 (Box 64, Folder 31)
  - Address to Atlantic Cotton Association, Augusta, Georgia, 1957 March 29 (Box 64, Folder 32)
  - “Congressional Record”, 1957 April (Box 64, Folder 33)
  - “Cowman’s Interest in Soil Bank Legislation,” Article in “The Cattleman Magazine”, 1957 April (Box 64, Folder 34)
  - “Farm Legislation,” TV Address for K-C-E-N TV, circa April 1957 (Box 64, Folder 35)
  - “A Reasonable Cotton Price Program,” Delivered at Farm Bureau Meeting, Dallas, 1957 April 24 (Box 64, Folder 36)
  - “Department of Agriculture Appropriation,” “Congressional Record”, 1957 May 15 (Box 64, Folder 37)
  - Reduction of the Budget, 1957 May 20 (Box 64, Folder 38)
  - “Secretary Benson’s Appearance before Committee on Agriculture,” TV Address for K-C-E-N TV, 1957 May 25 (Box 64, Folder 39)
  - “Congressional Record”, 1957 June 3 (Box 64, Folder 40)
  - A New Approach to the Problem of a Fair Income for Cotton Farmers, 1957 June 12 (Box 64, Folder 41)
  - “Proposed Cotton Price Programs,” Article for “Cotton Farming Magazine”, 1957 June 25 (Box 64, Folder 42)
  - July 4th Address in West, 1957 July 4 (Box 64, Folder 43)
  - “The Position of Farmers in American Society,” TV Address for K-C-E-N TV, 1957 July 4 (Box 64, Folder 44)
  - “Flood Prevention,” Delivered in Bruceville, Texas, 1957 July 5 (Box 64, Folder 45)
  - “Farm Legislation,” TV Address for K-C-E-N TV, 1957 July 27 (Box 64, Folder 46)
  - “Loans to Homesteaders and Desert-Land Entrymen,” “Congressional Record”, 1957 July 29 (Box 64, Folder 47)
  - “Congressional Record”, 1957 August (Box 64, Folder 48)
  - “Status of Soil Conservation Flood Prevention Projects”, 1957 August (Box 64, Folder 49)
  - Address before Farm Commodity Groups, 1957 August 6 (Box 64, Folder 50)
  - United States Agriculture, 1957 September 20 (Box 64, Folder 51)
  - Statement on Department of Agriculture, 1957 September 21 (Box 64, Folder 52)
  - Statement on Harold D. Cooley, 1957 September 21 (Box 64, Folder 53)
  - “Free Speech Necessary to Free Government”, 1957 October 1 (Box 64, Folder 54)
  - “A Workable Cotton Price Program,” Delivered to Tennessee Agricultural Council, Memphis, 1957 December 6 (Box 64, Folder 55)
  - “Cotton Speech,” Delivered in Taylor, Texas, 1957 December 19 (Box 64, Folder 56)
  - “Does Cotton Need Government Help?”, circa 1957 December (Box 64, Folder 57)
  - “The Death of Congressman Andresen of Minnesota,” “Congressional Record”, 1958 January 14 (Box 64, Folder 58)
  - “Congressional Record”, 1958 February (Box 65, Folder 1)
  - Address before Dallas, Texas Cooperatives, 1958 February 10 (Box 65, Folder 2)
  - “Congressional Record”, 1958 March (Box 65, Folder 3)
  - Article for “Cotton Trade Journal”, 1958 March 15 (Box 65, Folder 4)
  - “Education is a Problem of the School and of the Home,” “Congressional Record”, 1958 April 22 (Box 65, Folder 5)
  - “Statehood for Alaska,” “Congressional Record”, 1958 May 21 (Box 65, Folder 6)
  - “Commencement Exercises Speech,” Delivered before Meridian High School and Copperas Cove High School, 1958 May 23-26 (Box 65, Folder 7)
  - “Congressional Record”, 1958 June (Box 65, Folder 8)
  - July 4th Address in West, 1958 July 4 (Box 65, Folder 9)
  - Address at Waco Dam Groundbreaking, 1958 July 5 (Box 65, Folder 10)
  - Statement on Interparliamentary Union in Rio de Janeiro, Brazil, 1958 July 18 (Box 65, Folder 11)
  - Address and Newsletter for Interparliamentary Union in Rio de Janeiro, Brazil, 1958 July 28 (Box 65, Folder 12)
  - “Congressional Record”, 1958 August (Box 65, Folder 13)
  - “Cotton Legislation,” Delivered at Plains Cotton Growers, Inc., Lubbock, 1958 August 29 (Box 65, Folder 14)
  - “The Need of a Sound Agricultural Policy,” Delivered in Omaha, Nebraska, 1958 September 12 (Box 65, Folder 15)
  - “Feed Grain Legislation as it Affects the Cowman,” Delivered to Oklahoma Cattlemen’s Association, Oklahoma City, 1958 December 4 (Box 65, Folder 16)
  - “The Effect of the Agricultural Act of 1958 on Texas Cotton”, 1958 December 5 (Box 65, Folder 17)
  - Press Release on President Eisenhower’s Farm Message, 1959 January 29 (Box 65, Folder 18)
  - “Eulogy of Daniel F. Reed of New York,’’ “Congressional Record”, circa 1959 February (Box 65, Folder 19)
  - Address to Southeast Cotton Ginners Association, Atlanta, 1959 February 6 (Box 65, Folder 20)
  - “Agricultural Production Payments,” “Congressional Record”, 1959 February 12 (Box 65, Folder 21)